Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Wrestling Negatives, circa 1928-1982; 17
  - Teams, 67
    - Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06173)
    - Team, 1940, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06174)
    - Team, 1941, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06175)
    - Team, 1942, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06176)
    - Team, 1943, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06177)
    - Team, 1944, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06178)
    - Team, 1944 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04499)
    - Team, 1945, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06179)
    - Team, 1947 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04500)
    - Team, Freshman, 1954 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04501)
    - Team, 1954 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04502)
    - Team, 1956 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04503)
    - Team, 1962 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04504)
    - Team, 1963 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04505)
    - Team, 1965 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04506)
    - Team, 1966 Nov. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04507)
    - Team, 1967 Feb. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04508)
    - Team, 1967-1968 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04509)
    - Team, 1968 Dec. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04510)
    - Team, 1969 Feb. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04511)
    - Team, 1975 Dec. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04512)
    - Team, 1978 Jan. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04513)
    - Team, 1982 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04514)
  - Games, 68
    - Wrestling Action, 1938-1940, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06180)
  - Miscellaneous, 69
    - Robert E. Lee Prize Winner: wrestler Mike Jordan and ACC Award Winner, trackman Ed Stenberg, 1969 May (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04515)
    - Robert E. Lee Prize Winner: wrestler Mike Jordan and ACC Award Winner, trackman Ed Stenberg with Eddie Cameron and Dr. Robert S. Rankin, 1969 May (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04516)
- Volleyball Negatives, 1979-1991; undated; 18
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 70
    - Player, unidentified, action shots, 1979 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04517)
    - Player, unidentified, action shot (color), undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04518)
  - Teams, 71
    - Team, 1979 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04519)
  - Games, 72
    - Duke vs. UNC, undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04520)
    - Duke vs. unidentified, 1991 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04521)
- Undetermined Sport Negatives, 1937-1970; undated; 19
  - Individual Athletes/Coaches/Staff, 73
    - Aycock, Tom, undated, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06181)
    - Eby, John, 1966 Sept. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04522)
    - Gards, Bob, undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04523)
    - Harrison, Pat, undated, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06182)
    - Harrison, Pat, undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04524)
    - Lutz, Bobby, 1965 Mar. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04525)
    - Pennington, S. Wayne, undated, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06183)
    - Schwartz, [?], 1970 (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04526)
    - Snyder, Ronald Murl (Ron), 1970 May (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04527)
    - Storey, Ed, undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04528)
    - Walker, Stanley, undated (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04529)
    - West, Bobby, 1966 Nov. (Box 35, Item UA13020018-N-04530)
    - Williams, Westley, 1937, Nitrate (Box 40, Item UA13020018-N-06184)